theteacherscorner.net 2018-08-19

# Privacy Policy

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/theteacherscorner.net).  

 **The Teacher's Corner respects your privacy.  
**Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of The Teacher's Corner, except as required by law. 

**Credit card details  
**The Teacher's Corner currently offers a premium subscription service. We use PayPal (www.paypal.com) & Stripe (www.stripe.com) to process credit card payments and do not store _**any**_ credit card or bank information on our servers.

**External Sites  
**The Teacher's Corner may link to, or embed content from, external websites (i.e. YouTube.com, Facebook.com, etc). These external websites may collect information, embed their own tracking cookies, and/or evaluate your interaction with that embeded content. The Teacher's Corner is not responsible for the content or collected data of these external internet websites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information. 

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Registration Data**  
If you register on our website, we store your username, password, first name, last name and email address in our database. You can see, edit and delete your personal information at any time (except changing your username)by logging in and accessing your personal profile.

**Purchase Data & Credit Card Details**  
If you purchase a subscription on our website, we store a transaction ID and subscription expiration date along with your registration data. We use PayPal (www.paypal.com) and Stripe (www.stripe.com) to process credit card payments. No credit card or bank information is stored in our database.

**Puzzle & Worksheet Form Data**  
We have puzzle and worksheet applications on this website that require form data to be entered by the user. This data collection does not include any personally identifiable information, nor should any personally identifiable information be placed into these forms. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons  
**A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows The Teacher's Corner to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and The Teacher's Corner does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feed providers and advertising firms. 

We use third party advertisements on The Teacher's Corner to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can read more about it and/or opt out [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Your Privacy at Third Party Sites**  
Our privacy policy applies only to the theteacherscorner.net top level domain (TLD) and subdomains of this TLD, and does not extend to third party websites which may be linked from this site. Please read the privacy policy of third-party websites to learn how they collect and use information about you. 

**Children and COPPA**  
The Teacher's Corner maintains compliance with COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. All information on TheTeachersCorner.net is directed to adults who are at least 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years old, please do not submit any personal information through our website without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**  
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to The Teacher's Corner and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through The Teacher's Corner have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

**This privacy policy may be updated periodically as new technologies and web practices evolve. Any changes to this policy will be contained on this page and will always be available for our users to be informed as to how we use information that we collect.**

For any other information, email the [webmaster.](https://www.theteacherscorner.net/contact/contact.php?privacy)
